Benjamin Molini Vilhunen

PHONE (615) 425-6406 | EMAIL BENJAMIN@MOLINI.FI

LINKEDIN PROFILE [| WEBSITE https://molini.fi/ []

SUMMARY

Creative individual with a strong, demonstrated history of 8+ years in customer interactions as well as diverse experience in team leading and project management.

What motivates me the most is being able to see the concrete impacts of my work while doing something I am passionate about and creating something that aligns with my clients goals and expectations to make a positive impact and successfully drive their business forward.

Through extensive experience in various customer-oriented positions, I have accumulated valuable knowledge that can be seen in the results of projects I've worked on. I have great instincts, but being an analytical person, I always seek data for my decisions. Paying a lot of attention in research, I am good at executing even big ideas within given constraints.

HIGHLIGHTS

- Strategic Planning Experience
- Project Management
- Team Leadership
- Data Analysis
- Retail Service Plan Design and Execution
- Technology Savvy
- Comprehensive Organization Skills
- Strong Team Player
- Excellent Problem Solver
- Results-Oriented Leader
- Customized Solutions Capabilities

WORK EXPERIENCE

CELLULAR SALES

04/2021 - 07/2021 VERIZON SALES CONSULTANT

- Successfully engaged and drove new business and consumer-based account sales
- Consistently generated new business revenue while performing about 20% above given KPIs
- Delivered comprehensive technical sales support assistance
- Performed continuous account research to discover and and engage eligible sales targets
- Maintained close relationships across business and consumer accounts to cross-sell new solutions when appropriate

MOLINI.FI

04/2012-CURRENT FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER & FRONT END WEB DESIGNER

Since graduating, I have registered a business and through it provided multiple customers with various services across multiple projects including graphic & web design, branding, print media, video and sound design, photography and more.

HOLVI PAYMENT SERVICES OY

03/2020 - 03/2021 CUSTOMER SUPPORT SPECIALIST

Holvi is a Finnish Fin-tech growth company providing entrepreneurs with banking, accounting and bookkeeping services.

- Analyzed and monitored account usage patterns to identify and report risks and threats
- Collaborated with internal anti money-laundering and anti-financial crime teams to prevent illegal client operations
- Provided high-quality customer service over multiple channels to business banking customers while maintaining high client-confidentiality and safety procedures
- Performed higher than average on all major key metrics including tickets solved and customer satisfaction
- Studied and completed multiple anti-money laundering & financial crime prevention trainings
- Coached customer service team to optimize efficiency and boost employee performance
- Created support articles and customer service macros that aligned with the tone of voice and communication principles

SWAPPIE 0Y

01/2019 - 12/2019 RETAIL TEAM LEAD

08/2018 - 12/2019 CUSTOMER SUCCESS SPECIALIST

Swappie is a marketplace for buying and selling refurbished iPhones safely and affordably. In 2019, Swappie got an honorary mention from Sitra for the top circular economy company of the year in Finland.

- Planned and developed a new retail service design
- Designed and launched a flagship retail store
- Designed and deployed new systems to boost efficiency and sales
- Provided periodic performance reports and metrics
- Recruited and managed a team of 15 individuals across two retail locations
- Trained the team and maintained a level of high customer service standards

CHEAPSLEEP FINLAND OY

07/2016 - 12/2018 MARKETING SPECIALIST **07/2016 - 09/2017** FRONT DESK RECEPTIONIST

CheapSleep Hostel in Helsinki is the largest hostel in the Helsinki central metropolitan area.

- Designed captivating works to sell and promote products
- Launched social media campaigns and drove in new traffic
- Filmed and edited various ads to support a friendly company image

ACADEMIC WORK

12/2017 - 05/2018 JUNIOR IT CONSULTANT

Working as a consultant, providing graphic design & website development services for customers of AW. One larger project coordinated and finalised by me were the websites for Buying Service Oy.

TUI FINNMATKAT

04/2016-07/2016 GUEST RELATIONS HOST

I worked as a destination guide for TUI, the largest global tourism company. I worked closely with a multinational team of Guest Relations Hosts and together we were in charge of the comfort of our guests and with any issues during their holidays.

Tasks included quality control for the hotel, arranging excursions for guests and excursion sales.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

AUDIOVISUAL COMMUNICATIONS: MEDIA PRODUCTION AMMATTIOPISTO LUOVI - HELSINKI, FINLAND - 2012